{
    "subject": "resource/The_Clarks",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/linguistics/gold/hypernym",
    "object": "resource/Band",
    "human_readable": "The Clarks are a Band.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9800236821174622,
            "question": "Is The Clarks a band?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8741676211357117,
            "question": "What type of group are The Clarks?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8468212485313416,
            "question": "Are The Clarks known for music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.711006224155426,
            "question": "What is The Clarks?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6995241045951843,
            "question": "What genre of music does The Clarks play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6593604683876038,
            "question": "Are there any famous members of The Clarks?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5655917525291443,
            "question": "Do The Clarks perform live?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5459173917770386,
            "question": "Where is The Clarks from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4331836402416229,
            "question": "Do people listen to The Clarks?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19032110273838043,
            "question": "Has The Clarks won any awards?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Clarks are a Band.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4640_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Do people listen to The Clarks?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4640_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where is The Clarks from?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4640_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Do The Clarks perform live?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4640_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4640_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4640_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4640_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4640_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4640_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4640_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4640_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4640_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4640_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4640_87.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about The Clarks as an independent American rock band, including details on their members, history, and music. Therefore, the statement that \"The Clarks are a Band\" is supported by the context provided."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}